<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dabbawala</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_menu">Activity_menu</string>
    <string name="large_text">

        "Monday :"
        "---------------------------------\n"
         "Lunch - Dal, bhindi, roti, rice, salad, pickle.\n "
         "Dinner - Lauki kofta, aalu gobhi, roti, rice, salad, pickle.\n"
        "---------------------------------\n---------------------------------\n\n"


        "Tuesday :"

        "---------------------------------\n"

        "Lunch - Tamatar aalu, raita, roti, rice, salad, pickle. \n"
        "Dinner - Chana dal, mixveg, roti, rice, salad, pickle. \n"

        "---------------------------------\n---------------------------------\n\n"


        "Wednesday :"
        "---------------------------------\n"
        "Lunch - Arhar dal, brinjal aalu, roti, rice, salad, pickle. \n"
        "Dinner - curry, roti, rice, salad, pickle.\n"

        "---------------------------------\n---------------------------------\n\n"


        "Thursday :"
        "---------------------------------\n"
        "Lunch - Masoor dal, aalu matar, roti, rice, salad, pickle.\n"
        "Dinner - Chole masala, cauliflower, roti, rice, salad, pickle.\n"

        "---------------------------------\n---------------------------------\n\n"

        "Friday :"
        "---------------------------------\n"
        "Lunch - Arhar dal, cabbage, roti, rice, salad, pickle.\n"
        "Dinner - Soyachunks + aalu, baingan bharta, roti, rice, salad, pickle.\n"

        "---------------------------------\n---------------------------------\n\n"


        "Saturday :"
        "---------------------------------\n"
        "Lunch - Mix dal, methi aalu, roti, rice, salad, pickle.\n"
        "Dinner - Rajma masala, arhar dal, roti, rice, salad, pickle.\n"

        "---------------------------------\n---------------------------------\n\n"


        "Sunday :"
        "---------------------------------\n"
        "Lunch - Veg biryani, raita, paneer, roti, salad, pickle.\n"
        "Dinner - Chole bhature, kheer, salad, pickle.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text1">
        "Updated at 2022-03-07

Dabbawala ("we," "our," or "us") is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how your personal information is collected, used, and disclosed by Dabbawala. This Privacy Policy applies to our application named Dabbawala, and its associated subdomains (collectively, our "Service"). By accessing or using our Service, you signify that you have read, understood, and agree to our collection, storage, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service. \n"
        "Definitions and key terms

To help explain things as clearly as possible in this Privacy Policy, every time any of these terms are referenced, are strictly defined as:\n"
        "• Cookie: small amount of data generated by a website and saved by your web browser. It is used to identify your browser, provide analytics, remember information about you such as your language preference or login information.

Company: when this policy mentions "Company," "we," "us," or "our," it refers to Dabbawala, Near jain mandir vardhman colony Subedar ward sagar that is responsible for your information under this Privacy Policy.

• Country: where Dabbawala or the owners/founders of Dabbawala are based, in this case is India.

• Customer: refers to the company, organization or person that signs up to use the Dabbawala Service to manage the relationships with your consumers or ervice users.

• Device: any internet connected device such as a phone, tablet, computer or any other device that can be used to visit Dabbawala and use the services.

• IP address: Every device connected to the Internet is assigned a number known as an Internet protocol (IP) address. These numbers are usually assigned in geographic blocks. An IP address can often be used to identify the location from which a device is connecting to the Internet.

• Personnel: refers to those individuals who are employed by Dabbawala or are under contract to perform a service on behalf of one of the parties.

• Personal Data: any information that directly, indirectly, or in connection with other information

- including a personal - identification number - allows for the identification or identifiability of a natural person.

• Service: refers to the service provided by Dabbawala as described in the relative terms (if available) and on this platform.\n"

        "• Website: Dabbawala's site, which can be accessed via this URI

• You: a person or entity that is registered with Dabbawala to use the Services.

Information automatically collected

There is some information like your Internet Protocol (IP) address and/or browser and device characteristics - is collected automatically when you visit our platform. This information may be used to connect your computer to the Internet. Other information collected automatically could be a login, e-mail address, password, computer and connection information such as browser plug-in types and versions and time zone setting, operating systems and platforms, purchase history, (we sometimes aggregate with similar information from other Users), the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through and from our Website that may include date and
        prevention and other purposes. During your visits, we may use to- such as JavaScript to measure an collect session information including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page. We may also collect technical information to help us identify your device for fraud prevention and diagnostic purposes.\n"
        "We automatically collect certain information when you visit, use or navigate the platform. This information does not reveal your specific identity (like your name or contact information) but may include device and usage information, such as your IP address, browser and device characteristics, operating system, language preferences, referring URLs, device name, country, location, information about who and when you use our and other technical information. This information is primarily needed to maintain the security and operation of our, and for our internal analytics and reporting purposes.\n"









    </string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_privacy_policy">PrivacyPolicy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_string">Privacy Policy</string>
</resources>